Finding aid to Smith College Relief Unit records CA.MS.00095
Smith College Archives
- Individuals: V - Z
  - Young, Dorothy A., Jun. 1918-Jan.1919 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - War Experiences, undated (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - Photographs, Dec. 1918 (Box 151, Folder 19)
- News Clippings
  - 1917 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Jan. 1918 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Feb. 1918 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Mar. 1918 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Apr. 1918 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - May 1918 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Jun. - Aug. 1918 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Sep. - Dec. 1918 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - 1919 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - 1920s (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - other dates and miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box 152, Folder 11)
- Photographs: A - Z
  - Photo album of Isabel La Monte Hackett, 1918-1919 (Box 153)
  - The Argonne (Box 153, Folder 1)
    [See Individuals: Stevenson, photo album, pp.19, 20]
  - Bacquencourt, 1917-1922 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Beauvais, Spring; 1918 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    [See also Individuals: Biddlecome, photo album and Individuals: Stevenson, photo album, pp. 7-9]
  - Breuil, 1917 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Buverchy, 1917 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Canal du Nord, 1919 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Canizy, 1917 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Cemetaries, 1919 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Chateau Thierry, 1918 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Esmery - Hallou, 1917 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - M. Fussein, undated (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - German Prisoners, 1917-1920 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Grecourt (Box 153, Folder 13)
    [See Photographs: Grecourt]
  - Hombleux, 1917-1920 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Hombleux Band, 1920 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Hombleux Library, 1920 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Hospital, undated (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - Nissen, undated (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - Paris, 1918 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - Perrone, 1917 (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - Red Cross, 1917-1918 (Box 153, Folder 21)
    - William B. Jackson, 1918-1920 (Box 153, Folder 22)
  - S. S. Rochambeau, 1917 (Box 153, Folder 23)
  - Sancourt, undated (Box 153, Folder 24)
  - St. Quentin, 1917 (Box 153, Folder 25)
  - Verdun, 1918 (Box 153, Folder 26)
  - Unidentified, 1917-1929 (Box 153, Folder 27)
- Photographs: Grecourt
  - Automobiles, undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Barracks, 1917-1918 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Barracks, 1919-1920 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Chateau de Robecourt, 1917-1919 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Approach and Garden, 1917-1919 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Christmas, 1917 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Church and Mass, 1917-1923 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Farm Animals, 1917-1920 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - General, 1917 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Llanoy Farm, 1919 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Orangerie, Garage, 1917-1919 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Peasants and Children, undated (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Personnel, undated (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Marie Pottier, 1917 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - Robert Geuse, 1917 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - School, undated (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Social Service Worker, undated (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - Store and Traveling Store, 1917-1919 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - The Unit, 1917 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - The Unit, 1919-1920 (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - The Unit, general, 1918-1921 (Box 154, Folder 21)
- Publications
  - Alumnae News Bulletins, 1917-1918 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - An Irrepressible Crew (2 copies), 1968 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - correspondence, Nov. 1967 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Illustrations, undated (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Typescript, undated (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - SCRU Pamphlets, undated (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Smith Alumnae Quarterly, Nov.1917-Nov.1923 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - War Pamphlets and Publications, general, 1914-1940 (Box 155, Folder 8)
- Reconstruction
  - Argonne Association, 1920-1925 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Belleau Wood Memorial Association, 1928 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Boy Scouts, correspondence, Jul. - Dec. 1919 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - correspondence, (Miller) (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - correspondence, (Lewis) (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - correspondence, general, 1920 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - General, 1921 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, 1918-1920 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Bureau de Bienfaisance, 1921 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Eppevelle, 1919-1923 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Hombleux, 1922-1929 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Ecole d'Action Sociale, undated (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - Ecole de Florence Nightengale, 1921-1922 (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - Federation of American Agencies, Jun. - Jul. 1919 (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - French Restoration Fund, 1919 (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - Grecourt Church Bell, 1923; 1933 (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Photographs, 1923 (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - Salvation Army, Jan.1920-Feb.192119Secours d'UrgenceMay 1920-Dec.1921 (Box 156, Folder 18)
  - Secours d'Urgence, Jan.1922-Apr.1924 (Box 156, Folder 20)
- Anniversaries [Oversize Materials]
  - Index of Scrapbooks (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Anniversaries, 1967 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Album: Smith Overseas in WWI (Box 157)
    - (Book I), Apr.1917-Nov.1918 (Box 157)
    - (Book II), May 1919-Aug.1946 (Box 157)
- Out to Win by Coningsby Dawson, 1918
- Out of the Ruins by George B. Ford, 1919
- Stretchers: The Story of a Hospital Unit on the Western Front by Frederick Pottle, 1929
- The Officers and Nurses of Evacuation Eight by Frederick Pottle, 1929
- Vassar's Rainbow Division, 1918 by Gladys Bonner Clappison, R.N., 1964